What you do that?
He's a SCRAP MAN. OH YEAH.
Sick guy. Do you DO THAT [\h__\h] HEY. DO
YOU DO THAT HEY DO YOU
DO YOU DO THAT?
WHERE IS HE GONE?
EVERYONE REMEMBERS HIM. THAT WAS ONE OF
THEM. HE WAS WE WALKED PAST HIM.
REMEMBER HIM?
REMEMBER HIM? DO YOU REMEMBER HIM? DO
YOU REMEMBER HOW OLD ARE YOU THERE? 40
I'M older than you.
Yeah?
23 AND YOU REMEMBER HIM?
MATES. I think that's right. I think
that's how we all I think that's how you
can we're definitely in a simulation,
you know. Like
this is the matrix definitely. Cuz
there's no way that man survived long
enough to I'm [\h__\h] 44 and there's the
same fellow who's going hey
and I was a kid and he's [\h__\h] 23
there and he remembers hey
and it's not you mate and you work in
the game. Do you ever met the hey guy?
You met the hey guy? [\h__\h] off. [\h__\h] off.
No, YOU HAVEN'T.
HAVE YOU? IS IT ONE GUY?
THERE'S ONE GUY WHO JUST GOES HEY
AND I LIVED IN LIVERPOOL AS WELL. WHERE
DO YOU LIVE?
WHERE?
CHESTERFIELD? THE MAN WAS WALKING PAST
YOU NOW.
>> [laughter]
>> NO WONDER HE COULDN'T [\h__\h] PRONOUNCE
HIS WORDS. HE WAS [\h__\h] KNACKERED
MATE.
>> [laughter]
>> THAT'S pickled my [\h__\h] head that you
know.
>> [laughter]
>> You thought about him for years. I want
to find the hey guy now.